<Events>
    <Event>
        <Name>News</Name>
        <Type>Morning</Type>
        <Des>It's a brand new day! What will you do this lovely morning?</Des>
        <Choices>
            <rollChoice>Watch the news
                <Des>You decided to watch the news. Apparently there are some interesting rumors about the new iPhone. Maybe it's time for an upgrade.....?</Des>
                <DC>10</DC>
                <Type>WIS</Type>
                <Success>Maybe not. But you're excited to learn more about a future option!
                    <Effects>
                        <Effect>SAN
                            <Content>+5</Content>
                        </Effect>
                    </Effects>
                </Success>
                <Failure>You spent the whole morning googling about the rumor, which turns about to be some stupid rendering made by an art student.
                    <Effects>
                        <Effect>SAN
                            <Content>-2</Content>
                        </Effect>
                    </Effects>
                </Failure>
            </rollChoice>
            <Choice>Preview the next chapter of the textbook for your next class
                <Des>You decided to read the textbook. Ganing a preliminary understading of the material.</Des>
                <Effects>
                    <Effect>MOD
                        <Content>previewed</Content>
                    </Effect>
                </Effects>
            </Choice>
        </Choices>
    </Event>
    <Event>
        <Name>Overslept</Name>
        <Type>Morning</Type>
        <Des>You've overslept! A quick glance at Wooble map says you still have a slight chance of make it to class in time!</Des>
        <Choices>
            <rollChoice>Try to make it
                <Des>You try to get ready and grab your stuff as quickly as you can, and runs out of the door.</Des>
                <DC>15</DC>
                <Type>DEX</Type>
                <Success>Phew! You got in just before the professor did, and you didn't forget anything! But you didn't get to eat breakfast, and you're absolutely exhausted.</Success>
                    <Effects>
                        <Effect>SAN
                            <Content>-2</Content>
                        </Effect>
                        <Effect>MOD
                            <Content>panting</Content>
                        </Effect>
                    </Effects>
                <Failure>You forgot your wallet and your phone, going back to get them means you're surely going to be marked tardy.
                    <Effects>
                        <Effect>SAN
                            <Content>-5</Content>
                        </Effect>
                        <Effect>MOD
                            <Content>tardy</Content>
                        </Effect>
                    </Effects>
                </Failure>
            </rollChoice>
                <rollChoice>Fuck it. I'll just tell the professor about the "traffic nightmare!"
                    <Des>You try to spin a tale to convince your professor to let your tardiness slide for this time.</Des>
                    <DC>15</DC>
                    <Type>CHA</Type>
                    <Success>Your charming personality convinced your professor! Or he's just not paid enough to give a shit.
                        <Effects>
                            <Effect>mt
                                <Content>0</Content>
                            </Effect>
                        </Effects>
                    </Success>
                    <Failure>Your professor didn't buy a word you said. Fuck. Will he remember that you just lied to him?
                        <Effects>
                            <Effect>SAN
                                <Content>-10</Content>
                            </Effect>
                            <Effect>MOD
                                <Content>tardy</Content>
                            </Effect>
                        </Effects>
                    </Failure>
                </rollChoice>
        </Choices>
    </Event>
</Events>